你差点杀了我
You could have killed me!
我要为打中你屁股
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry
道歉多少次啊
for shooting you in the ass?
那是意外  你什么时候能忘记啊
It was an accident. When are you gonna let it go?
我能不用枕头坐的时候
When I can sit on my ass without using a pillow.
看来上次谈话之后
So, I take it - there's been little progress
你们没什么进展喽
since our last session.
就他的信任危机  是没有
No, not with his trust issues.
我没有信任危机
I don't have trust issues.
是他有嫉妒问题
He has jealousy issues.
最后一次说  我不嫉妒
Okay, for the last time, I am not jealous
你通过了警佐考试
that you passed the sergeant's exam.
跟我屁股上的洞洞说去啊
Tell that to the hole in my ass.
就是他打的那个...抱歉
The one that he put there, not the... I'm sorry.
-警探们  够了  -抱歉
- Detectives, please. - I'm sorry.
你们俩是要把性命交给彼此的人
You two depend on each other for your lives out there.
但就我看来
But from what I am seeing...
抱歉  但我要建议
I'm sorry, - but I am going to recommend
不再做搭档
that the two of you split up as partners.
-不不不  别那么做  医生  -别啊
- No, no... no. No, don't do that, doc. - No.
我们肯定还能试试别的办法吧
Yeah, there's got to be something else that we can try.
这个嘛
Well...
或许你们可以找个缓冲人
Maybe you could use some sort of a buffer.
缓冲人
A buffer?
小伙子们  你们怎么样啊
Hey, boys! How is it going?
抱歉  卡塞尔
I'm sorry, Castle.
你不能跟我们一起办案  哥们
Man, you can't work this case with us, bro.
我不是为了案子而来的
Yeah, I'm not here about the case.
明天是我和贝克特的
Tomorrow is the first wedding anniversary
第一个结婚纪念日
for Beckett and me,
我希望你们能分散她的注意力
and I was just hoping that you could distract her
好让我在办公室给她准备惊喜
while I set up a surprise in her office.
不好吧  卡塞尔
I don't know, Castle.
贝克特不希望你往分局跑
Beckett doesn't want you hanging around the precinct.
就是个小小的惊喜嘛
It's just a little surprise.
卡塞尔  你从不做"小"事
Castle, nothing you do is little.
嗯  估计会骑着大象进来
Yeah. Probably come in riding on an elephant.
然后带着她和大象
And then he takes her and the elephant
一起上热气球
up in a hot air balloon.
第一年是纸婚
Well, the first anniversary's paper,
不过这主意其实还不赖
but otherwise, that's not a bad idea.
等等
Wait a minute.
我们没吵架了
We're not arguing.
-他就是我们的缓冲人  -他就是我们的缓冲人
- He's our buffer. - He's our buffer.
我猜猜  治疗不顺利吗
Uh...let me guess... a little trouble in therapy?
我们需要有人跟着我们
Yeah, well, we need someone to follow us around
防止我们吵架
and keep us from fighting.
我也想啊  但是我好忙啊
I would love to, guys, but my schedule is just so...
我们帮你搞惊喜
We'll help you with your little surprise.
恭喜  你们找到缓冲人了
Congratulations. You got yourself a buffer.
我们去破案吧
Let's go solve a case.
你好啊  蕾妮  你今天可真美
Hello, Lanie. You are looking lovely today.
我天天都很美  卡塞尔
I look lovely every day, Castle.
你不能进去看尸体
And no, you cannot see the body.
为什么大家都认为我是为案子而来啊
Why does everyone assume I'm here about the case?
没事  他跟我们一起的
It's okay, Lanie. He's with us.
对被害人了解什么情况
So, what do we know about our victim?
名叫斯科特·麦考伊
Name's Scott McCoy.
据邻居说是失业演员
According to neighbors, he's an unemployed actor.
看上去是像演员
Sure had the looks for it.
至少凶手没伤他脸
At least - the killer spared his face.
但他的身体啊
His body, though... euggh.
九处刺伤
Nine separate entry wounds.
尸斑看是午夜到凌晨两点间死亡
Lividity puts the stabbing between midnight and 2:00 a.m.
九处刺伤  听上去像冲动杀人
Nine entry wounds? That sounds like a crime of passion.
是啊  要么就是凶手
Yeah, either that or someone wanted to be
不想留下任何隐患
really, really sure.
我们可能知道凶手是谁
And we may have an idea of who that someone is.
凶器被擦净  但鉴证组在凶手拿刀的
The weapon was wiped clean, but CSU found prints
刀架上找到了指纹
on the knife block where the killer got it.
在等待看是否系统里有呢
Waiting to hear if they're in the system.
好  我去跟进鉴证组
All right, I'll follow up with CSU.
莱恩  你找几个
Ryan, why don't you grab
警员  开始排查吧
a couple of unis and start a can...vass?
怎么了
What?
我懂了  我没"拜托"吗
Oh, I get it. I didn't say "Pretty please."
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
你什么都不用说
You don't have to say anything.
你就像死了狗一样丧着脸
You just mope around like your dog died.
卡塞尔  你是我们的缓冲人  缓冲吧
Castle, you're supposed to be our buffer. Buff.
嗯
Right. Um...
好吧  各位  角色扮演
Okay, guys, role playing...
你们都站在对方角度上想想
Each of you take the other's point of view.
这是久经时间考验的冲突解决办法
This is a time-tested method of conflict resolution.
我觉得这主意很蠢
I think that's a dumbass idea.
你还没试过呢
You haven't even tried it yet.
我是在装埃斯波
Oh, no, I-I was being Espo.
不错啊
That's good.
你也得承认  装得很像吧  埃斯波
Even you have to admit that was good, Espo.
但你没说"呦"
Only, you didn't say "Yo."
呦  我刚查到了指纹的匹配
Yo, I just got a hit on those prints.
名叫安东·福特
Guy's name is Anton Ford...
因重罪袭击而被录入系统
in the system for felony assault.
袭击  天呐
Assault? Well, jeepers.
希望他别太凶  我可敏感了
I hope he's not mean to me. I'm very sensitive.
我懂了  他在学我
Oh, I get it. Yeah, h-he's being me.
真好笑
Yeah, that's pretty funny.
走路是像神了
He did nail the walk.
他的体格是好
Yeah, his physicality's pretty good.
警监  查到了些嫌犯情况
Yo, cap. We got an update on that suspect.
安东·福特
Anton Ford.
他的指纹不仅满犯罪现场都是
Not only were his prints all over the crime scene,
还跟被害人斯科特·麦考伊有过结
But he had a history with our vic... Scott McCoy.
根据斯科特信用卡记录可看出是中城区一家酒吧常客
Scott's credit card makes him a regular at a bar in midtown.
我们查过  酒保说  两晚前
We checked... the bouncer said that two nights ago,
斯科特和安东大吵了一架
Scott and Anton got into a full-on brawl.
而且他俩不是第一次了
And that wasn't the first time that these two went at it.
上个月  也是这个酒吧还有一次
Last month, same bar,
而且两次都是为女人
and in each instance, it was over a woman.
那么安东喜欢女人和动手
So, Anton was a lover and a fighter.
但显然两样都不占上风
Yeah, but apparently, not very good at either.
两次他都被被害人揍扁
Both times, our victim kicked his ass
还被抢了妹子
and went home with the girl.
那么安东或许想复仇
Which means Anton - could have been out for revenge.
嗯  警员这就要把他带来
Yeah. Unis are bringing him in now.
我最喜欢的犯罪打击者怎么样了
How are - my favorite crime solvers?
你怎么来了
What brings you here?
你说我可以回来
Oh, you said that I could come back,
拿那幅被盗画作的  记得吗
retrieve that stolen painting...- remember?
是的  你得去趟
Yeah, uh, you know, you'll just have to go
二楼行政助理那儿
to the admin clerk on the second floor
填几份文件
to fill out some paperwork.
谢谢
Thanks.
很高兴
Oh, and it's so nice to see
里克又回来办案了
that Rick's back working cases again.
嗯
Um...yeah.
你为什么觉得他在办案
Uh, what makes you say that he's working cases?
二楼  行政助理
So, admin clerk, second floor.
谢谢
Thank you.
他是我们的缓冲人
He is our buffer.
你们的缓冲人
He's your buffer?
放开我  把手铐解开
Get the hell off me! Go on! Take these cuffs off!
那是我们的嫌疑人
And he's our suspect.
放开我  放开
Get the hell off me! Get off!
把手铐解开啊  看你还拽不拽
Go on! Take these cuffs off! See how tough you are!
你觉得带个警徽了不起了
You think that badge makes you special?!
那是嫌犯吗
That's our suspect?
我什么都没做
I didn't do nothing!
那个山一样的男人
How does that mountain of a man
怎么会被常人大小的斯科特揍扁啊
get beaten up by our human-size Scott?
而且是两次
Twice.
卡塞尔
Hi, castle.
我不是为了案子来的
Hey. Oh, I'm not here about the case.
我只是
I'm just, uh...
-来当缓冲人  -对
A buffer? - Yeah.
他们告诉我了  算是吧
Yeah, they told me -- sort of.
这是什么情况  心理治疗吗
So, what is this? For therapy?
好吧
Okay.
祝你们审讯好运
Well, good luck on your interview.
贝克特  说到审讯
Oh, hey, um, Beckett, uh, about the interview --
你介意跟我一起吗
Would you mind doing it with me?
人多力量大嘛
Three's a crowd in an interrogation.
当然  好吧
Sure. Fine.
惊喜行动开始  重复  行动开始
We are go for operation booyah. Repeat -- we are go.
还"小"惊喜呢
"Little surprise," my wounded ass.
你脾气挺大啊  安东
You got quite the temper, Anton.
那是因为我被激怒了
When provoked.
就像那晚在酒吧吗
Is that what happened the other night at the bar --
你被激怒了
You were provoked?
等等  你们抓我是因为我在酒吧打架
Wait. I'm -- I'm here for a bar fight?!
拜托  伙计
Come on, man!
要是这种理由也会被抓
If you're dragging people in here for that,
那纽约有一半人都得被你们抓起来
You're gonna have to arrest half the guys in new york.
不过纽约可没有一半人杀了斯科特·麦考伊
Except half the guys in New York didn't kill Scott McCoy.
而且鉴于有那么多目击者看到他打了你
And given all of the witnesses who saw him beat you up...
-两次  -你有动机
- Twice. - ...you had motive.
而且  他家里到处都是你的指纹
Plus, your fingerprints are all over his apartment.
他家有我的指纹是因为...
My fingerprints are there because...
因为...
Because...?
因为我们是朋友
Because we were friends.
斯科特
Oh, Scott.
卡塞尔  你弄完了吗
Yo, Castle, you done yet?
快了
Almost.
打架是设计好的  两次都是
The fight was staged -- both of them.
为什么要设计
Why were they staged?
为了帮斯科特泡到妞
To help Scott pick up women.
没听说过助攻手吗
You never heard of a wingman?
被打的助攻手
A wingman who gets beat up?
那只是我们的一个策略
It was just one of our tactics.
要是目标看起来会喜欢猛男型
See, if the target seemed like she was into macho guys,
我就会先去搭讪  表现得很粗鲁
I'd hit on her first, real aggressive.
然后斯科特就会来救她
And Scott would come to her rescue.
对  方式就是揍我
Yeah, by "Kicking my ass."
这么说他是个泡妞专家
So he was a pickup artist?
可以这么说
You could call it that.
斯科特喜欢有钱的已婚女人
Scott was into rich, married women.
他为什么要找已婚的女人
And why would he target married women?
他有什么目的
What was his game?
我不知道
I don't know.
他给了钱让我别问
He paid me not to ask.
这些女人  有没有你还记得样貌的
You think you can describe any of these women?
-我还需要多点时间  -好
- I need more time. - Okay.
安东审讯得怎么样
How'd it go with Anton?
莱恩会跟你细说的
Ryan will fill you in.
我更想听你说
I'd rather... hear it from you.
你俩现在关系恶化到这种程度了吗
Oh, it's that bad between the two of you?
对
Yeah.
我们会去查查安东的不在场证明
So, uh, we're gonna look into Anton's alibi,
但我们认为他可能不是凶手
But we don't think he was our doer.
其实他是在帮被害人
Turns out he was actually helping our vic
在酒吧勾搭有钱的已婚女人
pick up rich, married women in bars.
所以你们认为这些女人中的一个
So, you think one of these ladies
拿刀冲他发了疯
got ahold of a knife and went all psycho on him.
或者是她们妒火中烧的丈夫
Or one of their jealous husbands.
对了  贝克特
You know, Beckett...
安东还记得一些女人的样貌
Anton remembers - some of those women's faces,
我觉得要是找个速写画家来
So I-I think it would be a good idea
应该是个好主意吧
if we got him with a sketch artist.
你觉得呢
Don't you think?
可以  马上就能办
Yeah, and we will do just that
只要你们先让我进我的办公室
just as soon as you let me get into my office
我好打电话啊
so I can make that call.
我能走了吗
Now, may I?
贝克特  还有件事
Hey, Beckett. One more thing.
什么
Yes?
鞋挺好看
Nice shoes.
我错过了什么
Hey. What'd I miss?
是我的
Oh. That's mine.
这是...澳币
It's, uh... australian money.
卡塞尔  这太贴心了
Castle, this is very sweet.
这真是...太像你了
This is...very you.
可是
But...
我觉得这可能不是个好主意
I don't think - that it would be a good idea.
我知道我们现在是分离期
Look, I-I know we're on a time-out right now a-and --
可明天是我们的纪念日  我没法想象
but tomorrow's our anniversary, and I just can't bear
不跟你一起度过
the thought of spending it without you.
我很想去
I would love to.
真的很想
I really would.
你不知道我有多想
You have...no idea how much.
但是...
But I, um...
我担心那样对你不公平
I'm worried that it would be unfair.
因为无论晚餐有多美好
Because no matter how great dinner would be,
我还是得继续跟你分开
I would still need our time-out.
不  我明白
No. No, I know.
我不是想结束分离期
I'm not trying to put an end to the time-out.
我只是觉得能不能
I'm just saying, what if we could...
从分离期中分离出来一小会儿吗
have a time-out from our time-out?
没错
Exactly.
你意下如何
So, what do you think?
我很乐意明晚跟你一起用餐
I would love to have dinner with you tomorrow.
有时间吗
Got a sec?
被害人的财务状况有些疑点
I found something odd in our victim's financials.
什么疑点
What?
有一家空壳公司给他汇过款
Direct deposits from a shell corp.
有很多笔  每笔五千
There's a bunch of them -- 5 grand each.
最后一次是三天前
The last deposit was made three days ago.
也就是安东说
That's the same day that Anton said
他和斯科特在酒吧勾搭那女人那天
he and scott worked their bit on that woman in the bar.
这些钱大部分的到账时间
You know what? Most of these payments line up
都是安东说斯科特雇他的时候
with when Anton said Scott hired him.
听起来斯科特勾引已婚女人
Sounds like Scott wasn't picking up on
并不是为了取乐啊
married women for fun.
他应该是听命于人  从中获利  可为什么呢
Sounds like he was - getting paid for it. But why?
不知道
Don't know.
空壳公司那边还没什么发现
I haven't found much on the shell corp,
但他们有个地址
but they do list an address --
在上城区一个价值不菲的公寓
a pricy apartment uptown.
我打电话问了公寓管理员
And when I called the building manager,
他说斯科特是一年前开始租的
He said Scott rented it a year ago.
好吧  所以被害人是个失业的演员
Okay, so, our victim is an out-of-work actor
从一家神秘的公司收取神秘的报酬
Getting mystery money from a mystery corporation,
现在又多了一个神秘的公寓
And now - there's a mystery apartment.
还真是各种神秘啊
That's a lot of mysteries.
这家伙到底在做什么
What the hell was this guy into?
不管是什么  可能就是他被害的原因
Whatever it was, it might have gotten him killed.
惊喜
Surprise.
这地方比斯科特另外那个公寓可强多了
This place is so much nicer than Scott's other apartment.
估计他宁愿死在这里吧
Bet he would rather have died here.
可他要这公寓到底有什么用
Yeah, but why did he need it?
而且这里跟那个
And what did it have to do
付钱给他的空壳公司有什么关系
with that shell corp that was paying him?
抽屉都是空的
These drawers are all empty.
奇怪  就好像他只是想
Strange -- it's like he only wanted
伪装成他住在这里的样子
to make it look like he lived here.
也许他就是在这里跟那些女人啪啪啪的
Maybe this is where he was knocking boots with the married ladies.
夏洛克·福尔小子又开始推理了
Sherlock Homeboy's got a theory.
不好意思  你说啥
I'm sorry. What did you just say?
我说  这地方可真诡异
I said, "This place is really eerie."
-才不是这句  -好了  停
- That is not what you said. - Okay. Time-out.
二位  我要行使一下作为缓冲人的权利
Guys, in my official capacity as buffer,
我建议我们试一下别的方法
I'd like to recommend that we try something.
别再来角色扮演了
No more role-playing.
不  这是我第二任妻子金娜  和我
No, this is something my second wife, Gina, and I
用来避免争吵的办法
used to do to avoid arguments.
不要把想说的话立刻说出来
Instead of blurting out whatever was on our minds,
而是先写下来  过后再看看
we would write it down to revisit it later.
这样就不会因为冲动而说错话了
So nothing's said in the heat of the moment.
没错
Exactly.
我们发现
See, we found, with a little perspective,
一开始觉得很想要说的话
what seemed so important to us at first
过后就会觉得没那么重要了
was often quite trivial --
就像我们的婚姻一样
Sort of like our marriage.
好吧  你同意的话我也同意
Okay. I'm game if you are.
我发现点情况
Hey, I've got something.
看来这个空壳公司
Looks like this shell corporation
故意花钱雇斯科特去引诱有钱的已婚妇女
was paying Scott to seduce rich, married women
然后拍下他们幽会的证据
and get proof of their trysts --
应该是为了敲诈她们
Most likely to blackmail them.
好大的一个骗局
That's quite a racket.
或许还要人命了
Maybe a deadly one.
看来有些人不能惹[上]啊
Looks like someone did not enjoy getting screwed.
我是指被坑钱
Out of their money, that is.
里面没有SD卡了
There's no S.D. card in here.
WiFi打开了
It's Wi-Fi-enabled.
打印机也开着
So's this printer.
或许最后一次的照片还在内存里  看看吧
Maybe the last job is still in the memory. Let's see.
没错  是斯科特跟女人在床上
Yeah, that's Scott in bed with a woman,
可是看不到她的脸
But you can't see her face.
是的  不过看一下你能看见的
No, but look what you can see.
那是她的胳膊肘吧
I think that's her elbow.
不是  不是那个
No, not that.
她后背上的纹身
The tattoo on the small of her back --
是只蜻蜓
It's a dragonfly.
我们可以利用这个来确认她的身份
We can use that to I.D. her.
怎么确认  通过屁股来指认吗
How? Are we gonna do a butt lineup?
虽然这样挺有意思  但是我们不需要
As fun as that does sound, we might not need to.
安东给的画像出来了
Anton's sketches just came in.
瓦肯·西蒙斯的海洛因匹配到
So, where are you with matching Vulcan Simmons' heroin
现在的毒贩了吗
to current dealers?
毫无进展  得花一段时间
Nowhere. it's -- it's gonna take a while.
所以我觉得
Which is why I think
你跟卡塞尔去吃晚餐是个错误的决定
you going out to dinner with Castle is a mistake.
我知道
I know.
但是我很想他
But I miss him.
我明白
I get it.
可是如果让他知道了我们在做的事
But if you let him in and he figures out what we're doing...
我知道有什么风险
I know the risk.
我们查到些情况
Hey, we've got something.
通过安东提供的画像
Using a sketch that Anton provided,
我们确认了斯科特最近一个目标的身份
we were able to I.D. one of Scott's recent targets --
阿妮塔·斯迈思
Annika Smythe.
这不是那个搞对冲基金的人的名媛妻子吗
Wait -- the socialite wife of that hedge-fund guy?
她不是经常上小报吗
Isn't she in the tabloids all the time?
我们就是通过这个认出她的  而且我们
Which is how we recognized her and how we know
还知道了她正在离婚
that she's going through a messy divorce.
你已经知道阿妮塔了
You know Annika.
这里还有南希·安德伍德和克莱尔·史蒂文斯
Now meet Nancy Underwood and Claire Stevens --
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
都很有钱  而且都在离婚
both loaded - and going through divorces.
这里有一张她们三个人
There's a picture of all three of them
上周在资金筹集会上的照片
at a fundraiser last week.
这么说她们彼此都认识
So they know each other?
不止这样
Oh, more than that.
她们经常一起聚会
They hang out together.
实际上  根据阿妮塔的图片分享
Matter of fact, according to Annika's Instagram,
她们一会要一起去做水疗
they're going to a spa later.
你知道这意味着什么吗  贝克特
And you know what this means, Beckett --
这简直就是凶残版的《前妻俱乐部》
it's a murderous First Wives Club.
你觉得她们一起干的这事吗
You think they did this together?
为什么不是呢
Why not?
斯科特勒索了这些女人
Scott blackmails the ladies.
当她们拒绝付钱时
When they refuse to pay,
他就把这些照片给她们丈夫看
he shows the photos to their husbands.
然后丈夫们就会立即跟她们离婚
Who promptly divorce them.
这三个女人组团杀了斯科特
So all three women band together to kill Scott
因为他毁了她们的婚姻
for ruining their marriages.
这是最完美的解释
It is the perfect theory.
只不过这想法完全没有根据
Except it's completely unsubstantiated.
这简直...
That is...
是真的
true.
可是我们可以把她们叫来问话
But we can just have them in for questioning.
有什么理由呢
Based on what --
因为很像《前妻俱乐部》里面的情节吗
the plot of the "First Wives Club" movie?
不  当然不是
No. Of course not.
电影里面可没有杀人的情节
There was no murder in that.
可无论我们这么做  都要抓紧时间了
But whatever we do, we've got to do it fast --
以防她们各自跑掉
before they all scatter.
阿妮塔一直在发消息说
Annika has been posting
她今晚要飞去巴黎
about she's gonna be flying to Paris tonight.
我们要找到确凿的证据
We need to get some hard evidence
把死者跟她们其中一个联系起来
tying our vic to one of these women.
卡塞尔  你刚才说她们
Castle, you said that they were gonna
今天会去做水疗
spend the day at the spa?
是的
Yes.
在那个地方  纹身全都会露出来
Where all body art will be on full display.
如果其中一个有那样的纹身
If one of them has that tattoo...
那我们就能把她带回来了
Then we can bring them in.
不过我需要个搭档
I just need a partner to go with me
跟我一起去女更衣室
into the women's locker room.
女性搭档  各位
A female partner, guys.
画的文件我都弄好了
So, I got the paperwork for the painting all figured out.
只需要你再签个字  然后我就可以
I just need your signature, and then I'll be on my --
怎么了
What?
你好像压力挺大的
You look a little stressed.
不  我没有压力
No, I don't.
去做个水疗怎么样
What about a day at the spa,
就当是纽约警局对你的感谢
courtesy of the NYPD?
你们看到新闻上怎么说了吗
Did you see how it made the news?
是的  我打赌不光我们很高兴
Yeah. I bet we're not the only ones celebrating.
拜托  我们是来放松的
Come on, guys. We're here to relax.
目标已经出现
The regals have landed.
你觉得有纹身的是哪一个呢
So, which one do you think is our tattooed lady?
只有一种办法能确定
There's only one way to be sure.
我觉得你和你丈夫太一成不变了
Well, I think that you and your husband are just in a rut.
那样很安逸
It's just become comfortable.
可我不想安逸  我想要刺激
And I don't want comfort. I want edge.
那你就别太矜持  亲爱的
Then you got to spice things up a little, sweetie.
给自己纹个身
Get yourself a tattoo.
男人喜欢纹身
Men love ink.
他们会觉得你很放荡
Makes them think you're naughty.
得了吧  才不是呢
Oh, come on. That's not true.
你错了  纹身真的很性感
You're wrong. Tattoos are hot.
我们应该把你介绍给伊万  他是个天才
We should introduce you to Ivan. He's a genius.
天才
A genius?
这么说有点牵强吧
I mean, that sounds like a little bit of a stretch.
你自己看吧
Judge for yourself.
等等
Wait.
我是不是在哪见过你
Don't I know you from somewhere?
是的  你嫁给了那个作家  是吧
Yeah. You're married to that writer, aren't you?
你肯定是把我当成别人了
You know, I'm sure you're confusing me with somebody else.
不  她是个警察
No. She's a cop.
怎么回事
What's going on?
别装作你是来蒸桑拿的了
And don't pretend you're just here for a steam.
好吧  好吧
All right. Fine.
我们来是想问你们
We're here to ask you a few questions
和斯科特·麦考伊有什么关系
about your relationship with Scott McCoy.
找我们的律师去  亲爱的
Call our lawyers, honey.
我会的  但要先把你们带回警局
I will -- right after I drag you down to the precinct.
你们可以在图片分享上发自拍了
You can post a photo on Instagram.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
如果你有什么证据
If you really had anything on us,
你就不会来这里想办法看我们的裸体了
you wouldn't be down here trying to see us naked.
我们的确有证据
Oh, we've got something.
或者  应该说你们其中之一有
Or...rather, one of you does.
证据就纹在你们之中某个人的屁股上
And it's tattooed on one of your butts.
找到一个中头彩的
Got a winner.
没错  她在逃跑  裹着浴巾
Yep. She's running. In the towel.
停下  拦住她
Stop! Stop her!
不  不  别拦着我们
No! No, don't stop us!
找到了
Found it.
该穿上衣服了  水疗到此为止
Well...time to get dressed. Spa day's over.
不过我们走之前  你能把你的
Yeah, but before we go, can you please give me
纹身师的电话给我
the number of your tattoo artist?
你说得对  这家伙真是个天才
You're right -- the guy's a bloody genius.
那么在你们确认纹身的时候
And when you I.D.'d the tattoo,
是你们把浴巾拽下来的  还是它自己掉下来的
did you pull the towel off, or did it just...fall off?
实际上  是凯特把浴巾拽下来的
Well, actually, Kate pulled the towel off...
-好  -但我不大确定这有什么关系
- Right. ... - but I'm not quite sure how this is relevant.
你真可怜  哥们
You're pathetic, bro.
总得有人来写这份报告
Somebody's got to write this report.
那么海莉  你们追她一定
So, Hayley, it must have been pretty hard
追得很辛苦
for you guys to chase her
介于你和贝克特都裹着浴巾  对吗
'cause you and Beckett were both wearing towels, right?
给你  这是你的凭证
Hey. Okay, here you go. This is your voucher.
把这个拿到证据科去  那幅画就归你了
Just take that up to evidence, and that painting is yours.
好了  你们这些变态等会见
All right. I'll see you perverts later.
是的  会见的
Yes, you will.
莱恩正在试图获取
Ryan was trying to get details
关于你们走光事件的细节
on your wardrobe malfunction.
我  是你在问
Me? You were the one asking
贝克特是不是裹着一条浴巾
if Beckett was wearing a towel.
那是为了报告
That was for the report.
我以为卡塞尔在帮你们两个
I thought Castle was helping you guys
解决这个矛盾
resolve this conflict.
然后他回家了
Then he went home.
我有个嫌疑人得问话
Well, I have a suspect to interview,
你们两个必须解决这个问题
and the two of you need to figure this out.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
按照卡塞尔说的  写下来
What Castle said -- writing it down.
相信我  我要写的非常多
Trust me -- I got a lot to write.
希望我的笔不会没水
Hope my pen doesn't run out of ink.
没错  我和斯科特上过床
Yes, I slept with Scott.
以及没错  他照了照片  很明显
And yes, he took photos, obviously.
而之后他用这些来敲诈你
And then he used them to blackmail you.
敲诈  你从哪儿听说的这些
Blackmail? Where are you getting that from?
不然你那已经成为前夫的丈夫
Well, how else did your now-ex-husband
怎么会有这些照片
end up with these photos?
因为是我的前夫雇斯科特来和我上床
Because my ex hired Scott to sleep with me.
我们所有人身上发生了同样的事
The same thing happened with all of us --
阿妮塔和克莱尔
Annika and Claire.
你看  我们的丈夫想甩了我们
You see, our husbands wanted to trade us in
娶更年轻漂亮的花瓶
for younger trophy wives
却不想付出高昂的代价
without having to pay through the nose.
因为你们的婚前协议里
Oh, because you guys had infidelity clauses
有不忠条款
in your prenups.
我和斯科特的一夜情让我损失了一千二百万美元
My night with Scott cost me $12 mil.
你应该意识到
You do realize
你给了我一个谋杀斯科特的动机
that you just gave me a motive for Scott's murder.
我没杀他
I didn't kill him.
他的邻居认出了你
His neighbor I.D.'d you.
他说午夜的时候你站在那栋楼房外
He said that you were standing outside the building
就在斯科特被杀之前
at midnight just before Scott was killed.
所以  你想告诉我到底发生了什么吗
So, do you want to tell me what really happened?
我们在一起的那晚
The night that we had together
是我很久都没有体验到的一种感觉
was something I hadn't experienced in a long time.
结果发现自己不过是一票活儿
And to find out that I was just another paycheck...
所以我去找他对质
So I went to confront him.
但我都没有机会冲他吼
But I didn't even get to yell at him.
在我开口说话之前  他向我道了歉
He apologized to me - before I could get a word out,
说他做过那些事  真是糟糕透了
said he was a horrible human being for what he'd done.
他为什么突然回心转意了
And why did he have this sudden change of heart?
他说他从他最后一份工作中
He said that he had learned something
知道了一件事  一件很恼人的事
working his last job -- something upsetting.
那么  他有没有告诉你他最后一份工作是什么
So, did he tell you what his last job was?
是又一次色诱  不过他没说是谁
It was another seduction, but he didn't say who --
只说了他欺骗了一个好人
Just that he had screwed over a good person
而他想补救
and he wanted to make it right...
或许因此而死
Or die trying.
南希的司机证实了
So, Nancy's car-service driver confirms
南希离开的时候被害者还活着
that our vic was alive when Nancy left.
他12点15分把她送进车里
He helped her into the car at 12:15.
然后司机把南希一路送到格林威治
Then the driver took Nancy all the way out to Greenwich.
那么她不是我们的凶手
Okay. So she's not our killer.
也许斯科特的被害
Maybe Scott's murder has something to do
与他的最后一份工作有关
with that last job he was working.
让我们看看斯科特欺骗了谁以及被杀那晚
Let's see who Scott screwed over and what he was doing
他做了什么来试图补救
to make it right the night that he was killed.
我想我知道应该从哪里开始找
And I think I know where to start looking.
南希的丈夫和他的朋友们都雇了同一个律师
Nancy's husband and his friends all used the same lawyer
来终止他们的婚前协议
to bust up their prenups --
一个叫琳赛·特伦特的高手
some hotshot named Lindsey Trent.
《记事报》刚写了一篇关于她的文章
The Ledger just did a piece on her --
有钱不要脸之人的离婚律师
the divorce attorney to the rich and shameless.
要知道  如果她是雇佣斯科特的那个人
You know, if she was the one that was hiring Scott,
她一定知道他的最后一份工作是什么
she would know what his last job was.
但是没有搜查令
Well, yeah, but there's no way
她不可能对我们坦白
she's gonna talk to us without a warrant.
而我们没法获得  除非找到确凿证据
Which we won't get -- not unless we have something concrete
证明她与这些有关
to tie her to all this.
我早上给地检官打电话
I'll call the riding D.A. in the morning.
我们一起想想如何取得搜查令  回见
We'll brainstorm on how to get a warrant. I'll see you guys.
我们得换一种解决方式
We need to go at this another way.
要知道
You know...
也许找出斯科特最后一次色诱的方法
Maybe the way to find out about Scott's last seduction
是我们自己来一次引诱
is with a seduction of our own.
对啊
Right.
-我完全不知道你在说什么  -好吧
- I have no idea what you mean. - Ok.
让我来理一下
So, let me get this straight.
你们想让我去见一个离婚律师
You want me to see a divorce attorney --
明天  我的结婚纪念日
Tomorrow, on my wedding anniversary.
以客户的身份打探
To pose as a client.
不不不  我不赞同  理查德
No, no, no. I don't think so, Richard.
凯瑟琳知道这事吗
Does Katherine know about this?
不  而且  她也不会知道
Uh, no, no. And, um, she's not going to.
最好让她可以合理推诿
Best to give her, uh, plausible deniability
以防这个圈套不成功
in case this sting goes sideways.
不过我是喜欢成功的骗局
Though I do love a good sting.
你们需要他做什么
What would you need him to do?
律师们会把他们花在每一个客户
You know how lawyers keep a log
身上的时间记录下来
of all the hours they spend on each client?
当然  他们的时间记录精确到分钟
Sure. They keep track of their time down to the minute.
还有每个案子的每笔花销
And of every expense incurred on each case.
比如雇佣斯科特
Just like hiring Scott.
那么如果我能看到琳赛
So if I get a look at the last few days
最后几天的记录
in this logbook of Lindsey's,
我们就能知道斯科特的最后一份工作
We can figure out Scott's last job.
那么  你加入吗
So...are you in?
理查德·卡塞尔
Richard castle?
是的
Yes.
琳赛·特伦特  幸会
Lindsey Trent. Nice to meet you.
谢谢你能在临时通知下与我见面
Thank you for seeing me on such short notice.
离婚本身已经很有压力
Well, divorce is stressful enough.
找到一名律师不应该如此
Finding a lawyer shouldn't be.
我们回我的办公室去
Now, let's go back to my office,
我们看看我能为你做什么
and we'll see how I can help you.
路上如何  来的时候交通堵吗
How was your drive? Did you hit much traffic on the way in?
不  出乎意料地
Uh, no, surprisingly...
他进去了
He's going in.
卡塞尔当然会有一副实时监控眼镜
Figures Castle would own a pair of live-streaming glasses.
事实上  是贝克特送给他的
Actually, Beckett gave them to him.
-真的  -贝克特怎么了
- Really? - What about Beckett?
以及你们两个在这儿做什么
And what are you guys doing in here?
贝克特  搜查令有进展吗
Hey, Beckett! How's that warrant coming?
不走运  地方检察官说
You know, unfortunately, the D.A. said
我们没有足够的证据
that we don't have enough proof to, um...
你们看什么呢
What are you watching?
就是
Just...
黄片
It's porn.
你不会想看的
You don't want it.
你在这干很久了吗
Have you been here long?
这些是我们的新办公室
These are our new offices...
这是那个律师吗
Is that the lawyer?
那是从卡塞尔眼镜上传过来的实时图像
Uh, that is the live stream from Castle's glasses.
我真该跟你们的装修设计师聊聊
I should talk to your decorator.
你俩让卡塞尔去执行监视任务
So, you guys sent Castle on a surveillance mission
而我明明告诉过你们他不能参与纽约警局的案子
after I told you he was not to work any more NYPD cases.
我们觉得你还是不知道的好
We didn't think you should know.
我们只是想保护你
We were trying to protect you.
通过把我丈夫送到最好的离婚律师那吗
By sending my husband to the city's top divorce attorney?
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary?
你们知不知道这有多大的风险
Do you guys have any idea how risky this is?
这有可能会让整个案子功亏一篑
This could blow the entire case.
我们对此行动的知情及参与到此为止
Our involvement in and knowledge of this operation is over.
跟我说说  你和...
So, tell me -- what happened with you and, uh...
凯特·贝克特之间怎么了
Kate Beckett, right?
纽约警局警探是吧
The NYPD detective?
实际上她是警监
Oh, uh, she's a captain, actually.
她晋升得还挺快的
Oh. She moved up the ladder quickly.
对  她很擅长她所做的事情
Yes. Well, she's very good at what she does.
这就是你们之间出现问题的根源是吗
And that is the root of your problem, isn't it?
她太专注于工作
She's so focused on work,
没有多余的精力留给你是吗
She doesn't have anything left for you?
别表现得这么惊讶
Don't look so surprised.
这种事情
It's a story I've heard
我见得实在太多了
all too often.
但就像你写的故事那样  卡塞尔先生
But like the stories you write, Mr. Castle,
你可以选择如何结束这一切
You get to choose how this ends.
所以告诉我  你准备离婚吗
So, tell me -- are you set on divorce?
或者说还有希望
Or is there still hope?
这个
Well, um...
一个离婚律师问这样的问题还挺罕见的
That's a rather unusual question for a divorce attorney to ask.
我又不是非接这笔生意不可
Well, it's not like I need the business.
也对  我肯定
Right. Yes. I'm sure you're, uh...
肯定你很忙
...sure you're very busy.
我能  我能喝点水吗
Could I -- could I get some water?
当然
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢  喉咙有点干
Thank you. A little dry.
真的太对不起了
I am so sorry.
没关系
That's okay.
蒂凡尼  能拿点纸巾过来吗
Uh, Tiffany, can I get some towels?
小蒂
Tiff?
白痴
Idiot.
我去一下卫生间
Um, I'm going to go to the restroom
拿点纸巾过来
and just get some paper towels.
-好的  -好
- Of course. - Okay.
我是琳赛
This is Lindsey.
真的吗
Really?
谢谢你的提醒
Thanks for the heads-up.
是我在地方检察官办公室的朋友打来的
That was a friend of mine from the D.A.'s office.
是这样
And it, uh, it turns out
有人想申请搜查令来查我的客户名单
someone is trying to get a warrant for my client log.
没错  就是你的老婆
And -- oh, yeah -- it's your wife.
真的吗
Really?
真是太巧了
That is a crazy coincidence.
来真的吗  这只是个误会
Ser-- seriously, this is just a misunderstanding.
够了  我不是个傻子  但你肯定是
Okay, I'm not an idiot, but obviously, you must be.
你可糊弄不了我
There was no way you could fool me.
你抓得可真紧
Quite a grip you have.
强劲的手指
Strong fingers.
乔治·凯勒
George Keller.
根据琳赛的记录本
According to Lindsey's log book,
他是最后一个为斯科特的服务买单的人
he is the last person billed for Scott's services.
他和凯勒玩具公司有关联吗
Is he connected to Keller Toys?
他是整个凯勒帝国的董事长
He's the president of the entire Keller empire --
玩具  电子游戏  书籍  教育视频
Toys, video games, books, educational videos --
应有尽有
You name it.
这是个价值几十亿的公司
It's a multi-billion-dollar company.
以及一个拥有家族价值的品牌
And a brand - synonymous with family values,
很讽刺的是  他是个有名的花花公子
which is ironic - since he's a renowned playboy,
已经有第三任妻子
already on wife number three.
你说得这好像是个坏事一样
You say that like it's a bad thing.
有意思的是  凯勒上一次离婚
Oh, and here's a fun fact -- Keller's last divorce
他们的婚前协议被认定无效
featured a prenup that was nullified by --
你猜  是因为他妻子的不忠
You guessed it -- his wife's infidelity.
乔治·凯勒之前就找过斯科特
So George Keller has used Scott's services before.
假如斯科特勾引了现任的凯勒太太
And if Scott was seducing the current Mrs. Keller
但他突然心态转变
when he had his big change of heart...
他可能跟乔治翻脸  威胁要揭他底
He might have turned on George and threatened to expose him.
这就会损害整个公司的好名声
Which would have damaged the company's wholesome reputation,
所以凯勒杀掉了斯科特来封口
so Keller killed Scott to keep him quiet.
斯科特·麦考伊吗
Scott McCoy?
对不起  我不知道那是谁
Sorry. I have no idea who that is.
真有意思  因为你的第二任妻子知道
Well, that's funny, because your second wife did.
我给她看了照片
She recognized him
她立刻就认出来了
immediately after I showed her this picture.
想要忘记一个让你毁了婚前协议
Guess it's hard to forget somebody
损失几百万的人挺难的
who cost you millions in a broken prenup.
她到处乱搞又不是我的错
It's not my fault she slept around.
你买通了跟她出轨的人
You paid the guy that she slept with,
然后又想花钱让他帮你
then you hired him again to help you dump
甩掉现任的花瓶老婆  还能要个折扣
your current trophy wife at a discounted price.
你不知道自己在说些什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
我很清楚
I think I do.
别再说了  乔治
Not another word, George.
你必须立即释放我的当事人
You need to release my client right now.
我可不这么觉得
I don't think so.
任何你以为自己掌握的证据
Any evidence that you think that you have
都是非法获得的
has been obtained illegally,
任何凯勒先生所说的都不会被采纳
making anything that Mr. Keller has said inadmissible.
发什么了什么事
What's going on here?
你来告诉我吧  警监
Oh, well, you tell me, captain.
先是让你的丈夫来偷我的记录
First, you send your husband to steal my records,
现在你的警探又毫无理由地
and now your detective is questioning my client
在审问我的当事人
without cause.
你的当事人雇了我们的被害人和他妻子睡觉
Your client hired our victim to sleep with his wife.
事实上被害人和四个当事人的妻子都睡过
In fact, our victim slept with four of your clients' wives
就为了破坏他们的婚前协议
in order to blow up their prenups.
我想这个事实肯定会引起
That's a fact that I'm sure would be interesting
纽约律师协会的兴趣
to the New York bar association.
我们别跑题
Okay. Let's not get sidetracked here.
事实就是  你们调查的谋杀案
The simple fact is, you're investigating a murder,
跟我的当事人一点关系都没有
which my client has nothing to do with.
所以我们就该相信你的话
So we should just take your word for it.
当然不是
Of course not.
我会提供我当事人
I will provide my client's whereabouts
麦考伊先生被杀当晚的行踪
the night that Mr. McCoy was killed.
而你们必须搞清楚事实
And you guys need - to get your facts straight.
我并不想跟我妻子离婚
I'm not looking to divorce my wife.
我们下周末将会重新宣誓
We're renewing our vows next weekend.
你知道我们会调查这事的吧
You know we're gonna look into that, right?
来吧
Oh, please do.
事实上
In fact...
乔治
George.
我甚至会把给她价值两百万的
...I'll even send you the insurance papers
婚戒保险单发给你们
for the $2 million ring I'm giving her.
凯勒说的是事实
Keller's telling the truth.
他和他的第三任妻子下周末将在
He and his third wife are renewing their vows
加勒比海重证婚誓
next weekend in the Caribbean.
那两百万的婚戒是合法的
And that $2 million rock is legit.
我正准备说来着
I was just about to say that.
是吗  我以为你要跟她说
Oh, really? I thought you were about to tell her
你仍然在艰难地核实凯勒的不在场证明
how you're still struggling to verify Keller's alibi.
-我很艰难地在查吗  -对  就是
- Oh, I'm struggling? - Yeah, you're struggling.
你们倆  别闹了
You guys, come on.
伙计们
Guys!
跟我讲讲凯勒的不在场证明
All right. Tell me about Keller's alibi.
我还在试图确认
I'm still trying to confirm
斯科特被杀时  他在自己办公室的说辞
that he was at his office when scott was murdered.
在我们能够证实之前
Okay, well, until we can verify that,
他依然是嫌疑人
then he is still a suspect,
而且我有直觉  他在隐瞒着什么
and my gut says he's hiding something,
所以  找到它
so find it.
你的直觉从未出错
And your gut is never wrong.
我认识凯勒圈子里的一些人
You know, I know some people in Keller's circle.
我可以找人刺探信息
I could put my feelers out.
谢谢  卡塞尔
Uh...yeah. Thanks, castle.
乐意效劳
My pleasure.
小伙子们情况如何了
How are things between the boys?
不太好  实际上我有点担心他们俩
Not good, actually. I'm kind of worried about them.
他们会解决好的
Oh, they'll work it out.
他们已经在一起经历了太多
They've been through way too much together
不会轻易放手的
to give up on what they have.
你是个智慧的人  卡塞尔  而且心胸宽广
You're a wise man, castle -- with a big heart.
而且你的样子很好看
You're rather good-looking, too.
你估计得控制一下恭维话的节奏
You might want to pace yourself on the flattery.
还有一整个晚餐的时间呢
You've got a whole dinner to get through.
说啊  哈维  说出来
Come on, javi. Just say it.
相信我  你不会喜欢我的真实想法
trust me, you don't want to hear what I really think.
-说说看  -好吧
- Oh, bring it on. - all right.
你是个爱抱怨  缺乏安全感  善妒的小男孩
You're a whiny, insecure, jealous little baby
故意朝我屁股打一枪
who shot me in the ass on purpose!
你是个傲慢的  小心眼的野蛮人
And you are an arrogant, manscaped neanderthal.
那次我不是故意的
And it wasn't on purpose.
下一次我会故意的
Next time, it's gonna be.
够了  我要找个新搭档
That's it. I want a new partner!
我也是
Me too!
我们可不能就让他们这样了  对吧
Oh, we can't leave them like this, can we?
我去跟哈维谈谈
I'll talk to Javi.
我去试试能不能让莱恩冷静下来
I'll see if I can calm Ryan down.
晚餐改天再约
Rain check on dinner?
好吧
Yeah.
事情怎么会变成这样
How'd it all go so wrong?
我是说  前一天我们还是好搭档
I mean, one day, we're a team --
默契到可以补上对方没说的话
Simpatico, finishing each other's sentences.
然后就
And then...
你给他的屁股来了一枪
You shot him in the ass.
那是个意外  哈维
It was an accident, jav.
是吗  你确定吗
Oh, was it? You sure about that?
是的  在你内心深处你也相信的
Yeah. And deep down in your heart, you are, too.
那不重要了
It doesn't matter.
信任一旦消失了  就很难再建立起来
Once the trust is gone, it's really hard to get it back.
不  不是这样  深远的羁绊能够战胜一切
No, that's not true. A strong relationship can survive anything.
但没有任何羁绊能战胜秘密和谎言
No relationship - can survive secrets or lies.
现在你得把真话告诉埃斯珀西托
Now, you need to tell esposito the truth --
你的确感到受伤和嫉妒
that you were hurt and jealous
因为他通过了考试但你没有
that he passed the test and you didn't.
得了吧  他反复在我面前炫耀  记得吗
Forget that. He -- he rubbed it in my face, remember?
"埃斯珀西托警佐"
"Sergeant Esposito."
你得向他道歉
You need to apologize.
才不  我才不要向他道歉
Hell no. I am not apologizing to him.
-为什么不  -就在他射伤我之前
- Why not? - Even before he shot me,
他就是不能相信  我通过了考试而他没有
he couldn't believe - that I passed and he didn't.
你得让这事儿过去
You have to let it go.
我不能
I can't.
我没办法
是我那个认识乔治·凯勒的朋友
Oh! It's my friend who knows George Keller.
嗨 弗朗西斯
Hey, Francis.
不  足够了  我想要的就是这个  谢谢
No, that's good. - that's all I need. Thank you.
-再见  -怎么样
- Bye. - what?
原来乔治卷入了一场
Turns out George is involved
凯勒集团内部的权力斗争
in a power struggle over the keller empire
对手是现任CEO佩内洛普·凯勒
with present C.E.O. Penelope Keller.
他的母亲  对吗
His mother, right?
她建立了这家公司
She founded the company.
是这样的
Yes, she did.
她比起乔治是有优势的
Now, she has an advantage over George.
因为凯勒是个家族企业
Because Keller is a family brand,
而她的名誉一向无可指摘
she has an impeccable reputation.
等等  你不会是想说
Wait. You don't think...
没错  就是这样
Oh, yes, I do.
乔治雇了斯科特去引诱自己的母亲
George hired Scott - to honeypot his own mother.
我丈夫去年过世之后  我没有跟任何人在一起过
I hadn't been with anyone since my husband passed last year.
是时候开始新生活了  而且
It was time, and it was...
那很甜蜜
Lovely.
你对你儿子雇用斯科特来毁你名誉的事
So you had no idea that your son hired Scott
一无所知
to smear your reputation?
是的
None.
当你告诉我这些  我本该
I wish I could tell you I was more surprised
更惊讶的
when you told me,
但乔治一向都没有什么家庭观念
but family values have never been George's strong suit --
这也是我们最大的分歧
which is actually what our feud is about.
能详细解释一下吗
What do you mean by that?
乔治想要关闭所有的国内制造厂
George wants to shut down all the manufacturing operations
并把这部分业务迁移到海外去
in this country and send them overseas.
为了节省成本
To save money.
但是这样成千上万的工人会失业
But thousands of workers would lose their jobs.
而我是把这些人当作家人
I consider those people my family.
你对斯科特说过这些吗
Did you ever mention any of this to Scott?
当然
Yes.
他有很多事情做的很好
Among other things he did well,
其中一项就是擅长倾听
Scott was a wonderful listener.
为什么这么问
Why?
那晚他似乎经历了信任危机
Well, it seems like he had a crisis of confidence that night.
发生了一些事情  导致他想改变自己
Something happened that made him want to change his ways.
天呐
Oh, dear.
你知道吗  是有一些奇怪的事情
You know, there was something odd --
第二天  我找不到我的办公室门卡了
the next day, I couldn't find my card key to the office.
我当时觉得可能乱放在哪了
I just assumed I'd misplaced it.
有可能是斯科特拿走了吗
Is it possible Scott took it?
据凯勒公司的安全主管说
So, according to Keller's security chief,
晚上11:30有人用佩内洛普的门卡进了大厦
Penelope's card key was used to enter the building 11:30 P.M.
所以斯科特被杀当晚的确去过凯勒大厦
So Scott did go there the night that he was killed,
而且我敢打赌  他是去见乔治的
and I am betting you - it was to meet with George.
却带给他母亲的色情照片
But instead of bringing x-rated photos of mom,
而是反过来威胁要揭穿乔治的抹黑把戏
Scott threatened to expose george's illegal smear campaign.
于是凯勒跟踪斯科特回家并把他灭口了
So Keller followed Scott home and then silenced him.
这是个可信的故事
It's a solid theory.
唯一的问题是不符合事实
Only, it doesn't match the facts.
为了查证凯勒的不在场证明
In order to verify Keller's alibi,
我和维克拉姆排查了他办公室的监控录像
Vikram and I scrubbed security footage from his office.
它显示斯科特在11:30分到了那里
It shows Scott arriving at 11:30,
然后10分钟后他离开了
but then scott left 10 minutes later.
但乔治·凯勒待到了凌晨3点
George Keller stayed until 3:00 A.M.
凌晨3点  那是斯科特被杀后一小时
3:00 a.M. -- that's an hour after Scott was killed.
凯勒的不在场证明是成立的
Keller's alibi holds.
是的  但是伙计们
Yeah, but you know, guys,
凯勒即使没有跟踪斯科特回家
just because Keller didn't follow Scott home
并不意味着他没有参与其中
doesn't mean he's not involved somehow.
如果他雇了什么人去解决斯科特
Well, if he enlisted someone to kill scott,
那也应该是在斯科特出现
it would have to have been after scott showed up
并且威胁他之后
and threatened him.
埃斯波  你既然能搞得到
You know, Espo, you did manage to get
凯勒办公室的监控录像
security-cam footage from Keller's office.
应该也能查到他的电话记录  对吧
You think you could get some phone records, too?
琳赛·特伦特  你确定吗
Lindsey Trent? Are you sure?
是的先生  看起来她就是帮凯勒先生处理
Yes, sir, seems like she was Mr. Keller's go-to person
各种犯罪活动的得力助手
for all manner of criminal activities.
如果琳赛对她的任何客户设置了
If Lindsey was operating an entrapment scam
欺诈陷阱
for any of her clients,
我们事务所绝不知情  也完全不支持此做法
it was without the firm's knowledge or approval.
那么  你一定愿意帮我们查清楚
Well, then I'm sure you'll be happy to help us out.
当然
Absolutely.
莱恩  你跟这位先生
Ryan, why don't you go with this guy
去取琳赛的文件和电话记录
and grab copies of Lindsey's files and phone records?
没问题  警佐
Yeah, sure, sarge. Want me to
我要不要顺便给你带杯咖啡呀
get you a cup of coffee, too, while I'm at it?
我真高兴咱俩就快分开了
I am so glad this is almost over.
把这该死的本子放下
Put this damn pad away.
知道吗
All right?
已经无所谓了
It doesn't matter anymore.
好
Yeah.
你俩分手后房子归谁
So, which one of you gets the house?
又是你
You again.
又来骚扰我的吗  警探
Here to harass me some more, detective?
实际上  我是来带你回警局的
Actually, I'm here to take you in.
如果你这是试图取得我的客户记录的话
If this is your latest attempt to get access to my client log,
我告诉你  没用的
it won't work.
你还是不明白对吧
You don't get it, do you?
你因谋杀斯科特·麦考伊而被捕了
You're under arrest for the murder of Scott McCoy.
什么
What?
我为什么要杀他
Why would I possibly do that?
因为斯科特准备
'Cause Scott was about to blow the whistle
告发乔治·凯勒
on George Keller,
如果你的委托人因犯罪预谋被捕的话
and if your client's going down for criminal conspiracy,
你也跑不掉
well, you would, too.
这也太扯了
Okay, this is crazy.
你根本没有任何证据
You have nothing on me.
你可以把这话跟那位
Yeah, well, you can tell that to the judge
签署你家搜查令的法官说去
who signed the search warrant for your apartment.
鉴证科的人正在搜查你家呢
CSU's going through it right now.
如果你是无辜的  那你也就没什么好怕的
Now, if you're innocent, that won't be a problem.
但如果你捅了一个人九刀
But if you stab a guy nine times,
那你身上某处肯定沾上了血
you're bound to get some blood on you somewhere.
你也许把衣服扔了
You probably threw the clothes out,
可鞋子呢
but what about the shoes?
你把鞋子扔了吗
Did you get rid of them?
还是你只是把血擦掉了
Or did you just try to wipe them off?
血迹残留可是很顽固的
Because blood residue can be one stubborn son of a bitch.
像我刚才说的  我要带你回
Now, like I said, I'm taking you in --
-琳赛  冷静点  -闭嘴
- Lindsey, calm down. - Shut up.
-冷静点  -闭嘴让我想想
- Just calm down. - Shut up and let me think!
听我说
Listen to me.
你是个出色的律师
You're a brilliant lawyer.
你也许还有胜算
You might still beat this.
但你要是开了枪  那就得坐一辈子牢了
But if you pull that trigger, you're gonna go away forever.
退后  躲我远点
Stay back. Just stay away from me.
我不能那么做
I can't do that.
哈维
Javi!
凯文
Kevin!
我没事
I'm okay.
你的笔记本挡住了子弹
Your notepad stopped the bullet.
厉害吧
How about that?
所以你才把它放那对吧
Isn't that why you put it there?
你救了我一命
You saved my life.
在那疯婆子跑掉之前赶紧扶我起来
Just help me up before the psycho bitch gets away.
好  来吧
All right. Come on.
站住  纽约警局
Stop! NYPD!
不许动  我会开枪的
Don't move. I'll shoot your ass.
他会的  相信我
He'll do it, too. Trust me.
我还是没想到
I'm still surprised
你居然为这家伙挡了个子弹
that you jumped in front of a bullet for this guy.
我也是  我是说通常
Me too. I mean, normally,
这家伙总是磨磨唧唧的  哪有这么快
his slow-as-molasses ass is never that fast,
但他今天就"噌"的一下就挡我前面了
but he was just like -- like "Phoom!"
好了  乔治·凯勒呢
All right, what -- what about, uh, George Keller?
我们在机场截住了他
We picked him up at the airport.
琳赛供认这件事是他们俩合谋的
Lindsey confessed that, uh, they were in on it together.
他试图坐私人飞机出国
And he was trying to leave the country in a private jet,
所以结果可想而知
so there you go.
看来他再续婚约的计划
Well, looks like he's gonna have to
得推迟个
postpone renewing his vows
30年甚至一辈子了
for another -- what, 30 to life?
-没错  -是的
- Right. - Oh, yeah.
总之我得走了
Anyway, guys, I have to get going.
除非你还想让我
Um...unless you still want me to put in
提交换搭档的申请
those new-partner requests.
不  今晚就不用了
Nah, not tonight.
不过等这家伙当上警佐的时候
I'm gonna need somebody eventually
我早晚还是需要个新搭档的
when this guy gets bumped up to sergeant.
这件事没这么快
Well, that's not gonna happen anytime soon.
名单上300个人  我是第279号
I'm Number 279 on a list of 300,
所以咱俩得再赖上一阵子了
so we're gonna be stuck together for a while.
听上去不错
I like the sound of that.
如果你没意见的话
If that's cool with you.
当然
Yeah.
如果你不介意的话
If it's cool with you.
我不介意
Is it cool with me?
哥们  你替我挡了个子弹
Bro, you took a bullet for me.
你有妻子  你家里有个怀着孕的妻子
You've got a wife -- a pregnant wife at home,
你还有个需要你养的女儿
you got a little girl who depends on you,
可你仍然
and yet, you still...
过来
Come here.
我给你们俩点时间  抱歉
I'm just gonna give you guys a moment. Sorry.
你想不想到我家来  一起看无限制格斗
Want to come over, watch some UFC?
珍妮做了豆腐
Jenny made tofu.
听上去不错  我是说无限制格斗
I like the sound of that -- the UFC part.
结婚周年快乐  迟了一天没关系吧
Um, Happy Anniversary? A day late?
没事  或者是早了364天
Yeah. Or, um, 364 days early.
我买了咱俩的晚餐
I brought dinner for us.
莱米餐厅  太棒了
Remy's. Perfect.
里克  我只是想
Um, Rick, I just wanted --
等一下
Mm. Wait.
这不代表我们
Look, this doesn't mean that we're --
不  不  我知道
No. No, I know.
这只是咱俩分居中的暂停时间
No, this is just a... time-out from the time-out.
那么
So...
缠绵一下
time in?
这比我记忆中的还要好
That was even better than I remembered.
我得留几招在咱俩结婚第二年用
Yeah, well, I had to leave a few moves for Year 2.
里克
Rick?
当你潜入那个离婚律师办公室时
When you were in that divorce lawyer's office,
我在看
I was watching.
是吗  贝克特警监  我都不知道
Why, Captain Beckett, I had no idea.
我觉得自己受到了严重侵犯
I feel so violated.
我知道你只是在扮演一个角色
Look, I know you were just playing a role,
但是
but...
当她问你咱俩之间还有没有希望时
when she asked you if there was any hope for us
你什么也没说  那真是
and you didn't say anything, it was...
凯特
Kate.
我从未放弃过希望
I have never given up hope.
从我们相遇的第一天起
Not since the day we met.
在你叫我放弃前  这一点永不会改变
And that'll never change until you tell me it should.
那就别改变
Then don't change.
永远别变
Ever.
好的
Okay.
我得走了
I have to go.
看来分居又开始了
I guess the time-out's over.
是的
Yeah.
我很快回来
I'll be right back.
未知联系人
紧急  我有所发现  找个隐秘的地方然后马上联系我
你的电话刚才响了
Hey, I think your phone buzzed.
一切都还好吧
Everything all right?
没事
Yeah. Fine.
好了  回头见
Okay, I'll see you around.
再见
See you.
人人美剧「在线播放」
震撼上线
欢迎前往苹果商店
及各大安卓市场下载人人美剧客户端